I'd love to
but I have to
meet my little sister
Oh…
What about
this weekend?
I'm going
to my uncle's house
Next Monday
after school?
I have to go
to prep school
Ah, too bad
He's so persistent
I can't get closer to him
but I can't
grow distant either
But now
that I think about it
I might be free
next weekend…
Just keep
a suitable distance
Okay, I'll see you
next weekend
You've changed
Kim Hyeong-ju
What the hell
are you talking about?
You only care
about Hong Il-tak
Everyone's scared
of Lee Hyeon-wu
So what? You mad?
No, I'm just
stating the facts
Hey
Hong Il-tak is my friend
If you're going
to complain, get lost
That loser
S***, this is
really annoying
Do I keep looking out
for Il-tak?
What happened
after that school trip?
I must be crazy
I'll just buy him
a meal and end it
Hey, Hyeon-wu